本片系《26种死法》的续集，
再次由世界各地26位恐怖片先锋新锐导演各自拍摄26部风格迥异的恐怖短片，
每位导演被委派一个英文字母作为自己负责的拍摄任务
每部短片的片名须为以该字母所构成的单词，
导演们被赋予了充分的艺术自由和创作空间，
可以随心所欲讲述一个与该单词相关的死亡故事
片名：《26种新死法》
=====百度悬疑片吧字幕组=====
汉大将军袁绍   vittiger双鱼
亡灵的守护骑士 水浒三国金刚
出发
Okay.
靠
No.
尼玛
Come on.
嘿，伙计们，瞧这个
Hey, boys, look at this.
把牌放下，骚鞑子
Put the cards down, you cunts.
就这样，抚摸她的头发，继续，继续摸
That's it, touch her hair.Go on. Go on.
喔，不错
Oh, yeah.
不错，不错，这俩母狗颜值真高
Yeah, yeah.Two fuckin' beautiful faces.
舌吻
Kiss her.
对，就这样
Yeah. That's it.
对，咪咪绝赞
Yeah. Fuckin' tits.
妈的，害什么臊！
Don't fuckin' care.
三周后
怎么有股怪味？
What is that fucking smell?
你笑一笑会死啊？
Would it kill you to smile?
妈的劳资一个月6000块，租了这种茅坑一样的破地方
Fuckin' $6,000 a month to rent this place and it stinks like shit.
A:《生手》
导演：E·L·卡茨（代表作：《死魂盒》编剧，《尸体解剖》编剧）
嗨，我是彼得·托兰，欢迎来到“托兰大世界”
Hi, I'm Peter Toland,welcome to "Toland's World".
这周我们来到诺丁汉郡的“发霉山谷”
This week we're in Elderberry Vale in Nottinghamshire,
一个正在蓬勃发展的传统英国乡村
a thriving stretch of classic English countryside,
确切来说是无数土生土长动植物的家园
home to literally thousands of indigenous plants and animals,
比如有已逾400年的猪獾洞穴
including a 400-year-old badger sett,
它们世代以来把这个山丘都挖成筛子了
which has crisscrossed this hill for untold generations.
但是近两年来猪獾都绝迹了，因为。。。
But in the last two years, the badgers have disappeared because
一个暗影降临了山丘，它是这么个模样的。。。
a shadow has fallen across this hill,a shadow in the form of this...
摄像头能挪开了吗？喂？
Are you gonna pan off me?Hello?
能把镜头对准发电站吗？要么。。。
Are you going to pan to the power station? Or...
行了，卡！彼得，我们得剪掉这段
Yeah OK, cut!Sorry, Peter we gotta cut there.
不，不，别剪，别剪
No-no, don't cut.Do not cut.
怎么了？
What's happening?
抱歉，之前我们失焦了几次所以...
Sorry, we lost focus a few times earlier so...
嗯？我们失焦还是你失焦了？
Yeah? We lost focus or you,you lost focus?
我...再来一次我能做好的，彼得
I... I could... I could do with another crack at that, Peter.
-抱歉
-Sorry, yes.
-你能做好？再来一次
-Could you? Another crack.
嗯，这是怎么回事？
Well, what's going on?
你对焦失败了，这才是关键所在
You lost focus.That's the whole point.
你就是干这一行的，对吗，布莱恩？
That's your job, isn't it, Brian?
我们没想到
We just didn't realize
你来回走动那么频繁所以...
you were going to move around so much so...
我当然要来回走动，我选择，我喜欢
Of course I move around,that's my style.
有些幅度实在太大了
There were some quite large movements.
我们送你根香肠尝尝，彼得，如果这...
We could whack down a sausage for you, Peter, if that's...
我不吃什么狗屁香肠，自己拿去用吧
I don't want a sausage.Shove it up your ass!
不...你瞧，我是说，也许...
No... Look, all I meant was,maybe there's...
不，阁下，让我来给你一些人生经验，如何？
No, look, Don, let me explain how this works, OK?
我叫约翰
It's John.
随你叫什么，我要来回走，你跟着我拍
Whatever your name is.I move around, you follow me.
这就是“托兰大世界”的风格，如同翩翩起舞
That's the way it works on Toland's World, it's like a dance.
- 懂否？
- OK?
- 嗯，明白了
- Yeah I get it.
那我们应该剪掉重来还是...
So should we cut now and go again, or...
不...不，我说卡你再停，这是规矩
No... no, I say cut,that's how it works on the show.
明白了吗？除非我说卡，不然一直拍
OK? I call cut and until then we keep filming.
明白了吗？嗯，这就是规矩
You got that?Right, that's how we roll.
- 行吗？好
- Alright? Good.
- 妥，欧了
- OK, yeah.
真是杠王
Prick.
听着，老实说不要发愁
Look, honestly,don't worry about it.
这就是个沙文主义秀
It's just a little alpha male display
都会过去的，我保证
and it'll all blow over,I swear to you.
你瞧，他知道你和阿滕伯勒共事，对吧？
Look, he knows you worked with Attenborough, right?
所以他觉得，觉得地位有点受威胁
So he just feels,he just feels a bit threatened.
哦，对，都是为了银豹奖
Oh, right, it's all about the Silver Leopard Awards.
嗯，他有点杠人，你干的不错
Yeah, he's a bit raw.Well done though.
干的漂亮，真的漂亮
Good work. Really good work.
- 嗯，庆祝一下
- Yeah, cheers.
- 那么，他认为他应该..
- What, so does he think he should
-获得奖杯还是...？
-他被提名了三次了
-have won them or...?
-He's been nominated three times,
眼下他认为阿滕伯勒在拆他的台
and now he thinks Attenborough's rigging it.
我明白了，明白了
I know, I know.
那是什么？
What was that?
别说话，让我听听，嘘
Hang on, let me listen,let me listen, hang on.
贪婪的小动物
Greedy little buggers.
瓦屋
Whoa.
你还是...你搞明白没，布莱恩？
You still...You getting this, Brian?
嗯...是猪獾
Yeah... the badgers.
有意思吧？有意思
Having fun are we? Big fun.
玩耍时间，带我玩耍带我飞
Fun times. Clue me in.Let's have a laugh.
- 彼得，这里还有猪獾
- Peter, the badgers are still here.
- 依然獾特猪
- The badgers are still...
不，由于发电站的毒气，猪獾都死了
No, the badgers are dead because of the toxins from the power station.
刚刚只是一段小插曲
That's what the episode is about.
- 你瞧，我们把这放进...
- Look, we put the...
- 放进什么？
- Put what?
我认为拍摄不能再继续下去了
I don't think we should carry on filming.
你听着，你算老几？你最后才闲庭信步地走过来
Listen, you. Who are you anyway? You waltz in here at the last minute,
-发号施令
-我可没有闲庭信步，你...
-calling the shots.
-I didn't waltz in anywhere. You...
我不想再听你扯淡了，行吗？
I don't want to hear any more from you, OK?
但是听着，彼得
But listen, Peter.
能听懂人话吗？
Can you hear me?
我意思是你来真的？
I mean is this for real?
当然来真的，还得更真一点
Of course it's real,and it's gonna get more real,
因为马上就有人要挨揍了
because someone's gonna get punched in a minute.
你看
Look, please.
听着彼得，我只是想提供帮助
Listen Peter,I'm just trying to help.
我不再想听你说任何废话
I do not wanna hear one more word from you.
我不说话难道还发短信？
Shall I text you? Or...?
哦，噢
Oh. Ow.
我不想站在这，拉我一下
Well don't just stand there.Give me a hand.
佛祖啊
Jesus!
彼得，彼得！
Peter! Peter!
彼得，沃妮马！
Pete, oh, God!
彼得？
Peter?
我了个艹
Oh, Jesus.
卡。。。。
Cut...
B:《獾》
导演：朱利安·巴拉特（代表作：《神奇动物管理员》系列）
安静！安静！安静！
Quiet! Quiet! Quiet!
大家安静，安静
People, settle. Settle.
我们会主持正义但不是在这里
Justice will be done but not here.
弗莱彻·鲍威尔，本庭判处你有罪
Fletcher Powell,this court finds you guilty
罪名是谋杀了露西·威尔逊
of the murder of Lucy Wilson.
我没有杀她！我没杀她！
I didn't kill her!I did not kill her!
你们放了我！
You need to let me go!
你们得报警！狗屁法律！
You need to call the police.Fuck law!
你们得以合法途径解决这件事！唯一的途径！
You need to deal with this the right way! The only way.
本地所有问题都是内部解决
All local matters are dealt with internally.
你懂的，这事关法律
You know that.This is a matter of law!
你们不要越级办事！
Your authorities do not stretch to those boundaries!
巴克利...
Barclay...
如果你立刻认罪，我们会致电有关部门
If you confess now, we shall call the proper authorities.
如果你抵赖，今天下午就会被处决
Deny, and you will be executed this afternoon.
- 不要停！
- Don't stop!
- 带他去他娘的小树林里去！
- Take him to the fucking woods!
好吧，我杀了露西
Very well. I killed Lucy.
我把她的尸体沉在了爱丁顿江上游的肯尼特河里
I dumped her body in the River Kennet beyond Eddington.
这就是你们想要的结果，这就是我的供认
There you go. There's my confession,
-现在报警吧！
-now call the Police!
-滚你他妈的臭傻逼！
-You fucking shit!
报警啊！是你们说的！你们保证过的！
Call the Police.You said! You promised!
你们都听到他说的了！
You all heard him!
你们都可以作证！
You all bore witness!
你将被本庭带到刑场
You shall be taken from this court to the place of execution,
斩立决
with no further delay.
今天午饭时间的头条新闻
The main headlines this lunchtime...
失踪超过一个月且被认为已经遇难的露西·威尔逊
Lucy Wilson, missing for over a month and presumed dead,
在东约克郡被发现，且安然无恙
has been found alive and well in East Yorkshire.
这位14岁的小姑娘和她26岁的男朋友私奔
The fourteen year old had run away with her 26 year-old boyfriend,
目前其男友已被当局控制
who has been arrested by local authorities.
大家听我说！她还活着，露西还活着！新闻报道了！
Hey guys, she's alive. Lucy's alive!It's all over the news!
快点，挂五档！
Come on, faster!
怎么着？你们打算把我像不会说话的动物一样射倒吗？
So this it? You're just gonna shoot me down like some dumb animal?
大哥我错了，别杀我，大哥，我求求你了！大哥
Oh Jesus Christ, no, please!
不要啊！
Don't do this!
神父，你劝劝他们吧！我求你了！
Father, don't let them do this...
please!
亲爱的道友，全真的上帝以其公正之名
Dearly beloved,it hath pleased Almighty God
对你进行审判
in His justice,to bring you under sentence -
并以法律之名定罪
and condemnation of the law...
把他按倒
Hold him down.
你们不能...求求你们，你们不能杀我！
You can't...please, you can't kill me!
神父，让他们住手！
Father, please stop!
你将如此被执行死刑
You are to suffer death in such a manner
他人将因你的死亡而受到警示
that others,warned by your example
或将更加害怕犯罪
may be the more afraid to offend.
噢！卧槽！
Oh, fuck!
他娘的托比亚斯，你砍得不够劲！
What the fuck Tobias,you didn't hit him hard enough!
我他娘的给他来个透心凉，看招！
I'll hit him a-fucking-gain then,won't I!
我操你妈，你差点把我手指头剁掉！
Oh fucking hell,you nearly took my fingers off!
那你他妈就站远点！
Well fucking move back then!
恪守礼仪，小伙子们！给他应有的尊严！
Decorum, boys!Give this man his dignity!
神父，闭上你的破嘴！
Father, shut the fuck up!
看在上帝的份上，结束这一切吧！
For the love of God, finish this!
补刀
Finish him off.
我们在此祈祷，上帝
And we pray, God,that you may make such use
您施加惩罚到人间，并拯救他的灵魂
of your punishments in this world that your soul may be saved
-让来世洗清罪恶
-in the world to come.
-你拿到一血了
-You're blooded now.
露西·威尔逊，失踪超过一个月并被认为已遇难...
Lucy Wilson missing for over a month and presumed dead...
我没有杀她！
I did not kill her!
C:《死刑》
导演：朱利安·吉尔比（代笔作：《孤独的死亡之所》）
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
看起来不错
Looking good.
生命归你了
Life is yours.
现在你得偿还我
Now you must pay me.
为新生命做出偿还
You pay for life.
D：《驱除》
导演：罗伯特·摩根
“倒酒”
E：《均衡》
导演：亚历桑德罗·布鲁格斯（代表作：《僵尸胡安》）
请不要...
闭上你的臭嘴！
去吧，你去叫人吧，你去吧
我会去的！你给我闭嘴！
抱歉...
我以为你想集万千“太黑啦”于一身
“太黑啦”是什么鬼？
荣耀
那你就说“抢人头”嘛
你啥意思？
如果你开枪的话
你的朋友们就会过来
抢走你俘虏“以色列婊子”的功劳
你叫什么名字？
没名字！
那我给你起个名字吧
穆罕默德
老土
与其被他们抢功劳
不如自己爬上树来
割掉绳子，押送我去村庄
莫非你怕高？
我才不怕高，你这以色列婊子！
证明给我看
我可是从飞机上跳下来的
让我看看你怎么爬树
如果这就是你跳伞水平
我看你顶多也就是个烧菜的厨子
瞧着，谁怕谁啊
你笑什么？
我又不会把你放了
我急着想尿尿
女人
你不知道怎么憋尿吗？
别尿到裤子里去了...
F：坠落
导演：亚伦·凯沙莱斯和纳沃特·帕普沙多（代表作：《大坏狼》）
你确定这是干邑白兰地？
Are you sure this is Cognac?
喝起来跟超市卖的便宜货一样
Tastes more like supermarket cooking brandy.
相信我，这是好酒
Trust me, it's the good stuff.
我不知道怎么说，爷爷
Yeah, I don't know, Granddad.
我感觉我的尿都比这好喝
I've done wee-wees tastier than this.
这...是...好...酒
It's... the... good... stuff.
噁！
Yuck!
你应该在这儿安个电视机
You could've got a TV in here.
我说过了，我不喜欢看电视
I've told you, I don't like telly.
搞台小的也行
Well, just get a small one then.
这儿就像五十年代一样
It's like being in the 1950s in here.
哦，你听说过五十年代的堕落事情吗？
Oh, have you heard something rotten about the 1950s?
看看你，我可爱的小孙子
Look at you,my lovely little grandson.
不再是以前的小孩子了
Not so little these days.
内啥，这也太尴尬了吧
Hello, this is embarrassing.
是的...
Right...
娘的，老夫得上床去了
I'm fucking off to bed.
哦？这条项链？嗯，这是纯金的
Oh? This necklace?Yeah, it is real gold.
挂在你的奶头上更漂亮，亲爱的
Would look even better hanging off your tit, love.
我绝对会灰常灰常喜欢的
And I am absolutely loving it.
“我可爱的小孙子”
"My lovely little grandson".
真娘炮！
What a twat!
你就是娘炮，兄弟
You're the twat, mate.
谁叫我娘炮？
Who called me a twat?
-哈啊？
-Ahh?
-哈啊，娘炮
-Ahh, twat.
哎哟我操！
Ahh, shit!
哎哟我操，娘炮
Ahh, shit, twat.
啊？！你在这儿干什么？
What are you doing in there?
噢，我每晚都在这儿
Oh, I'm here every night
你搞的我整晚都睡不着觉
and you keep me awake all night.
一直在那打飞机放屁，娘炮同志！
With your wanking and your farting.
Twat!
你想变的和我一样？
Are you trying to look like me?
是的，没关系吧？
Yes, is that alright?
-你手指头上是什么？
-What have you got on your finger?
-我在乍得搞到的
-I got this in Chad.
用来翘贝壳用的
It's for opening mollusks -
我爱屎它了
and I'm absolutely loving it.
嘿，这句是我的口头禅！
Hey, that's my catch phrase.
你脑子有毛病吧，爷爷？
What is your fucking problem,Granddad?
你就是毛病所在
You are my fucking problem.
你跟我在一起住整整一年了
You've been staying with me for a whole year now
你在挑战我的极限
and you're cramping my style.
我听你在电话里老说我是撸管狂魔
I heard you, on the phone calling me a wanker.
我？撸管狂魔？你不知道这话让我多难受
Me, a wanker.You don't know how that hurts.
瞧！你给我翻译翻译，我他妈的拿什么撸？！
Look, can you see anything that I could wank with?
雷港啊！你倒是翻译翻译啊！
Can you? Can you? Can you?
说啊！
Can you?
G：《爷爷》
导演：吉姆·霍斯金
H：《脑洞大开》
导演：比尔·普莱姆顿（代表作：《变种外星人》，《我嫁了个怪蜀黍》，《很黄很暴力》）
妈！蛋！
Ma! Die!
我们都他娘的老了！
We're fucking old!
把钱给我们！
Give us our money!
死吧！烂货！
Die, bitch!
我！操！
Aw, fuck!
你们想要遗产吗？
You want your inheritance?
来吃这个吧！
Eat this!
去啊！去拿啊！
Go on! Take it!
拿走了事！
Let's end this goddamn thing!
- 为什么叫我去！她怎么不去！
- Why me? She should take it!
- 没门！
- No way!
年纪最大的去拿！
The eldest should take it!
操你妈！
Motherfuckers!
想让我变得跟这老不死的一样吗？
Want me to get as old as that wrinkly bitch?
让我好好休息吧
Let me rest now.
我都一百二十岁了
I'm one hundred and twenty years old.
来拿呀！哇哈哈！
Take it, please!
你这死老太婆！
Fucking old cunt!
我们不要你的钻石了！
We don't want your stone!
你和它一块下地狱去吧！
Take it with you to hell!
这套房归我
I should get this house.
琦塔，那套海滨别墅归你
Chita, you get the beach house.
大哥，我也要那套海滨别墅
Brother, I also want the beach house.
你们就拿现金好了
Get cash instead.
我炒股需要现金
My share should be in cash.
谁想要我的集邮册？
Who wants my stamp collection?
你麻痹的怎么还不死！快死啊！去死啊！！
Inheritance my ass! Die already! Please!
我要取首饰盒
I'll pick the casket.
来人，通知律师
Somebody call the lawyer.
琦塔，海滨别墅归你
You can have the beach house.
你们拿现金吧
you're getting cash instead.
I：《老不死》
导演：埃里克·马蒂（代表作：《末日杀神》）
爸！！
Dad!
你这奸诈的恶魔！
You deceitful demon!
现身吧！奸诈的恶魔！
Come forth, deceitful demon!
现出原形吧！
Manifest yourself!
出来！
Come out!
以耶稣之名！
In the name of Jesus!
快滚，恶魔！
Be gone, demon!
快滚！
Be gone!
滚粗！撒旦！以耶稣之名！
Be gone, Satan!In the name of Jesus!
滚粗！恶魔！
Be gone, demon!
滚出来！恶魔！
Out you come, fiend!
上帝啊！
God!
七重黑暗滚出！强卡撸啊滚出！！
Out Seven Darknesses!Out Tranca Rua!
泽·皮林恰滚出！
Out Ze Pilintra!
净化吧，我主，把这块罪恶之地净化成全新圣地！
Transform, Lord,this Sodom into a New Jerusalem!
你体内有恶魔
There's disease inside of you.
我们把你带到这是为了驱除它
And we brought you here to cure it.
不要抗拒上帝给你的爱，孩子
Do not resist the love of God, boy!
那恶魔寄生在你体内
The Evil One set down a dwelling in you.
我们驱逐了堕落的灵魂
But we cast out his spirit of depravity!
接受吧！接受吧！
Accept this! Accept this!
耶稣正看着你，脸不要乱动！
Don't turn your face to Jesus!
他看得见你身上所有的污秽！
He sees all your filth!
你的，还有那个同性恋的
Yours and that other faggot's.
他已经被驱除了
Only that one's already gone down.
现在正被地狱业火焚烧
He's burning in hell now.
撒旦在嘲弄我们！
This is Satan mocking us!
这是他的一个小把戏，牧师
That's a trick, Reverend.
这是战争，牧师！
This here is war, Reverend!
不！不！不！不。。。
No! No! No! N...
爱情即法律
LOVE IS THE LAW
我很怕纹身
I'd be scared to get one of those.
肯定很痛
Hurts too much.
痛个屁
Fuck the pain!
仁慈的主
God of Mercy...
我将您的圣十字标识
I brand this lamb...
烙印在这孩子身上
with your holy cross
如此他便会记住您的爱
so that he remembers your love...
也会记住您的愤怒
But also your wrath!
爱情即法律
LOVE IS THE LAW
J：《耶稣》
导演：丹尼森·罗马里奥（代表作：《恶魔化身》编剧）
K：《丧钟》
导演：克里斯蒂娜·伯基特和布鲁诺·桑珀（代表作：《消失的浪潮》，《女收藏家》）
不许告诉大王巫师的占卜
我，埃萨高，会告诉他王子已被献祭
这样后宫妃子们会生出更多的男丁
我的女王！
放开他
欧定弯，你想抗旨么？
动手吧！
执行大王的命令！
这是她的阴谋，殿下
她密谋想当乌比尼国
下一任大王的母后
放了他
乌比尼
同此畜生切齿之疼
乌比尼应与之共痛
这咋的了这是？
不造啊，老哥
我一下惊呆了
大错已铸
占卜师亦遭此罪
我等正遭
毒咒的侵袭
欧吉索·奥沃多
是王子的毒咒
L：《遗留》
导演：兰斯洛特·易马苏恩（尼日利亚）
《26种新死法》
=====百度悬疑片吧字幕组=====
汉大将军袁绍   vittiger双鱼
亡灵的守护骑士 水浒三国金刚
34分钟之前
操他妈的，我去搞点药
Fuck yeah, I'll do some bath salts.
M：《咬肉》
导演：罗伯特·布切克
你的新娘在等待，永远在等待
嘿，我喜欢你拍的视频
Hey, I liked your movie.
你喜欢我的吗？
Did you like mine?
哦，我喜欢你的
Oh, I liked yours.
嗯？哦我刚打了个盹
Huh? Oh, I was taking a nap.
我准备好了
I am ready.
恩，装扮好了
Yeah, I am dressed.
我不会迟到的，好吗？
I'm not going to be late,alright?
哦买噶
Oh, my God...
倒计时：滴答，滴答，滴答，滴答
师傅，你这是最快的路线吗？
Excuse me, is this the fastest route?
小姐，今晚是万圣节，人特多
It's a busy night, lady.
乔治在那，所以是啊，我知道
George is there, so yeah,I know,
离婚后他们就再没见过面
they haven't seen each other since the divorce.
对吧，我勒个去，我真想在那
Right? Ah, man I want to be there for that.
你看着点行不？我可不想缺胳膊断腿
I'd like to get there in one piece, if you don't mind.
是，喏，我大概10分钟内能到
Yeah, okay, I should be there in ten minutes.
嘿，我们就不能绕道避开游行人群吗？
Hey, shouldn't we be avoiding downtown with the parade and all?
我说真的，你还是走路过去更快
I'll be honest. It would be better if you took a walk.
嘿，我听不到你说什么，我在骑自行车
Hey, I can't hear you.I'm on the bike.
我很快就到
I'll be there any second.
一，二，三，四，五
One, two, three, four, five.
- 科学怪人！
- Frankie!
- 嘿你们好啊
- Hey, what's up guys?
- 哟，科学怪人啊，你好拉风啊
- Yo Frankie, you're famous!
- 谢谢，谢谢
- Thank you, thank you.
不行，城区太堵了
It's impossible to get across town.
这出租车司机太不靠谱了
I don't think my cab driver knows what he's doing.
转角遇到爱
嘿你好啊
Hey there,
我可以给你拍张照吗？小骷髅怪
can I take a picture of you,scary guy?
给我也拍一张吧
You can take mine.
我喜欢你的装扮
I like your costume.
好了，泰姆，咱们得去妈妈那了
Okay.We have to go meet your mom.
哦，等下，等等
Oh, wait, wait.
谢谢你
Thank you.
过红绿灯，然后靠边停下来
Just get us through the light,and pull over.
随你便，小姐
Whatever you want, lady.
N：《关联》
导演：拉瑞·凡斯登（代表作：《恐怖之源》，《错身姐妹》）
死刑！
请宽恕我！不要！雅妹罗！球多麻袋！
我是人类！你们都是丧失！
放开我！我没的选择！
饶了我吧！
下一个！
被告：宫崎华奈
在最近爆发的“活死综合症”期间
被控与多宗故意谋杀罪有关
谋杀？
等，等一下
在2018年，当你女儿麻衣感染“活死综合症”时
你枪杀了她
然而这些谋杀均由可以恢复感染者的
新型药物"Z-cu"作出证据提供
但这种药物根本就没有研发出来啊
起诉方请求对被告执行死刑
但他们想要吃我啊！
我这是正当防卫啊！
那么你认罪吗？
没，没有
阿诺。。。我是你的法庭指派辩护律师
在这种情况下，你最好保持安静...
这就是"Z-cu"疫苗
田中先生，请问是谁杀了您？
啥？啥？啊！！！
正如在座各位所见
毫无疑问
被告有罪！
可我从来没见过这个脑袋啊！
等等
对于你们人类所犯下的罪行
在场所有人都是被害者
但我没有杀害你们中的任何一个啊！
你觉得这有差别吗？
你们人类对我们所做的一切，我们都铭记于心！
站住！
让我走...
麻衣...
你还活着？
太好了！佛祖保佑！
麻衣？
法官大人，请容我传唤第二目击证人
你支持被告所说的
“那些谋杀属于正当防卫”的言论吗？
是的
麻衣！
但是。。。
大多数情况下，她享受杀戮他们的快感
麻衣。。。你在说什么？
死刑！
无异议！
等一等
麻衣！麻衣！
妈妈，为什么你不把我安葬了呢？
麻衣！麻衣！麻衣！
不！
你们这群大丧失。。。。
我们该杀光你们！
你们该死！该死！该死！
老娘要杀了你们！
杀了你们！杀了你们！杀了你们！
麻衣。。。
麻衣！麻衣！！！！
O：《暴民统治》
导演：大畑创（代表作：《怪谈新耳袋百物语》）
谁有火柴？
Does anyone have matches?
我有
Yeah, I got some.
我，我，我们离开前谁拿了地，地，地图？
D- d-d-did anyone grab a m-m-map before we left?
不，不，不好意思，科，科，科比，我，我忘记了
Sh-sh-sh-shucks K-K-K-Kirby,I f-f-f-forgot.
你，你，你还记，记，记得吗？波，波，波佩
D- did you f-f-f-f-f-forget too,P- Poppy?
波佩也忘记了
Yeah, Poppy forgot too.
蜡烛的气味闻，闻，闻起来真赞，是什么，波，波，波佩？
Boy that candle sure st-st-smells G- Good, what kind is it, P-P-P-Poppy?
波佩的最爱，这是葡，葡，葡，葡，葡
It's Poppy's favorite,it's P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-P-
葡，葡萄味的
P- grapes.
那，那，那，那，那是什么？
Wha-wha-wha-wha-wha-wha-what's that?
只有一条路可以出，出，出，出去！
Only one way to fi-fi-fi-fi-fi-fi-find out!
科，科，科，科比，我不喜欢这
K- K-K-K-Kirby,I don't like it out here.
什么都看不见
Can't see a thing.
快看，这里有一个肌肉男和一个小婴儿
Hey look, it's a beautiful muscular man with a teeny-tiny baby.
我，我，我们要不要叫，叫，叫，叫醒他？
Sh-sh-should we wa-wa-wa-wa-wake him up?
嘿，哈罗
Hey, hello.
波佩？你还有火，火，火柴吗？
Poppy?Do you have any more m-m-matches?
有
Yep.
快，快，快点，等一下下
Now-now-now,just wait a minute here.
怎么了？
Say, what gives?
人呢？人呢？
Hello? Hello?
你们都到哪去了？
Is anybody out there? Anybody?
人呢？
Hello?
你们去哪儿了？啊！
Where did everybody go? Oh!
啊？波，波，波佩？巴，巴，巴特？
Huh? P-P-Poppy? B-B-Bart?
P：《结巴吓人》
导演：托德·罗哈尔（代表作：《自然召唤》，《爱的阶梯》）
一周七天
Seven days of the week.
12“S”意味着
12 "S" of the
黄道十二宫的标识？
12 Signs of the Zodiac.
在米国，你能和你寡妇的妹妹结婚吗？
In the United States,can you marry your widow's sister?
我以前听过这个，不能，因为题干里这个“你”已经挂了
Oh, I've heard this before.No, because you're dead.
你侄子的哥哥和你的哥哥是什么关系？
What relationship is your nephew's brother to your brother?
前者是后者的侄子
That's his nephew.
正确，第3组三字母数列缺少的是哪个字母？
Great. What is the missing letter in the 3rd three-letter sequence?
A, B, C. B, B, D.A,E,什么？
A, B, C. B, B, D.
A, E, F.
正确
Correct.
不好意思，我们能不能稍微加快一点进度，我必须。。。
Sorry. Can we wrap this up pretty soon? I need to...
说真的，你答的很棒！
Actually, you're doing very well.
我觉得你绝对值得继续答题
I think it's worth your while to stick around.
真的？
Really?
好吧，我觉得我现在很困惑
OK, cause I kind of feel like I'm locked in now.
好像需要头脑轻松一点
Like, I'm in a good head space.
假设大前天是星期六之后的第三天，那么今天是星期几？
The day before the day before yesterday is three days after Saturday.What day is it today?
额…星期一，星期二，星期三，星期四…
Uh... Monday, Tuesday,Wednesday, Thursday...
是星期五吗？
Friday?
完全正确
Correct.
现在我快速给你看两张卡片
Now I'm going to show you two flashcards.
你要告诉我它们是相同的还是不同的
You tell me if the images are the same or different.
相同？
Same?
不同？
Different.
不同，这太明显了吧
Different. Noticed that one quick.
很好，附加题
Alright.One more question.
判断题，过山车限高
True or false. A roller-coaster has a minimum rider
4尺
height of four feet tall.
约翰尼身高是三尺六寸
Johnny is three feet six inches tall
吉米身高是四尺六寸
and Jimmy is four feet six inches tall.
杰克比约翰高但是比吉米矮
Jackie is taller than Johnny and shorter than Jimmy.
杰克可以坐过山车
Jackie can ride the roller coaster.
-对还是错
-True or false.
-杰克可以坐过山车？
-Jackie can ride the roller-coaster.
比吉米高？
She's taller than Jimmy?
比吉米矮，比约翰尼高
Shorter than Jimmy.Taller than Johnny.
好吧，只能是对是错，是吗？
OK, so all these have to be true-false, right?
刚才说过了是“判断题”
This question reads, "true-false".
好吧，我可以说没有答案吗
OK.Can I say, "unanswerable",
或者说这是道脑筋急转弯，是不是这样？
or "trick question",or something like that?
这是什么推理？
Under what reasoning?
因为我们不知道杰克到底比约翰尼高多少
Well, you don't know how much taller.
可以是一寸
Like it could be, y'know, an inch.
也可以是两尺
It could be two feet.
根本没有衡量标准
I'm like looking at your face for clues.
没错
That's alright.
我知道了
So yeah,
最后的答案就是没有答案
my final answer is the question is unanswerable.
非常好，对了
Excellent, that is correct.
恭喜，一份完美的答卷
Congratulations,that was a perfect score.
如果你现在跟我走
If you can come with me right now,
我会给你一个难得的工作机会
I'd love to talk to you some about career opportunities.
太棒了，我很愿意
Great, I love opportunities.
妥，那走吧
Great, let's go.
Q：《问卷》
导演：罗德尼·阿谢尔（代表作：《第237号房间》）
不是这样的
照我说的做
把它摁成直角，坚定点
否则就死不了
管它呢？反正这密室里啥都没
对母鸡
你想让她躺在桌子上朝头上一枪？
示范给我们看
轮到你了，不许作弊，已经上膛了
如果已经抠扳机两次
米歇尔死的概率有多大？
四分之一
概率是四分之一
三分之一
记住
用力按，用正确的角度
一半对一半
还有机会，不是吗？
我爱你
是通往地下室的门！
他们听到了枪声！
或许没那么糟
我们得救了
R：《俄罗斯轮盘》
导演：马文·科伦（代表作：《群魔乱舞》，《血色研究站》）
嘿，亲爱的
Hey baby.
抱歉，打搅你睡觉了？
Hey, sorry, did I wake you?
没，没关系
No, no, it's fine.
还好吧？酒店怎么样？
How are you? How's the hotel?
很土豪，很奢华
It's fine, yeah it's alright,it's quite plush.
抱歉昨晚没有给你打电话
Urm... look, I'm sorry I didn't call last night,
忒忙，脱不开身
I just got stuck with these people...
没关系，会议怎么样？
It's OK. So how was the meeting?
还可以，挺顺利的，有些事还没谈好
Good, no it was really good,not everything is nailed down,
不过应该差不多了
but pretty much I think we've got a done deal, so...
不错，恭喜你
That's great, congratulations.
那你今天回来吗？我想你
So are you coming home today?I miss you.
不造啊，今早还有一个会议
Not sure, there's another meeting this morning but...
如果进展顺利，我搭晚上飞机回来
If that goes well then I should be on the night flight.
是门铃吗？
Is that the doorbell?
你约了人吗？
Were you expecting anyone?
没有啊
No...
你是谁？
Who is this?
撒宁啦？
Who is it?
-喂，侬撒宁？
-Hello, sir...
-是谁？
-Who is it?
我不知道…
I don't know...
侬组撒？
What do you want?
谁？他想要什么？
Who is it? What do they want?
请你马上离开否则我报警了
Please go away or I'm calling the police.
-怎么回事，蜜莉恩？
-What's going on, Miriam?
-我不知道…
-Don't know...
发生什么事？
What was that?
天啊，他拿了把锤子，破门而入
Oh my god, he's got a hammer.He's breaking the door.
-啊！他闯进来了
-Oh, he's breaking in. He's...
-什么？！
-What?
他正在砸门！
He's opening the door.
喂？麻烦转999
Hello? Give me the police.
英文服务
The English police.
快点，快点
Come on... Come on...
这里是999，有什么可以帮助你？
999, which service?
民警同志
Police.
请马上派人去我家
You need to send somebody to my home,
有人破门而入
an intruder's broken in.
请问你的名字和地址
What's your name and address?
我叫罗伯特·沃尔特斯，家住伦敦玛丽女王路35号
Robert Walters,35 Queen Mary Road, London.
你在家吗，先生？
Are you at the property now, Sir?
没有，我他妈在法国
No, I'm in fucking France.
我和我老婆还在保持通话，麻烦快派人过去
I'm on the phone to my wife,now please send someone.
老婆？
Miriam?
警察马上来了，你没事吧？
The police are on their way,are you OK?
我在浴室，不要说话好吗？
I'm in the bathroom,just... just don't speak, OK?
蜜莉恩？快回话！
Miriam? Talk to me!
蜜莉恩，你没事吧？说句话！
Miriam, are you OK?Talk to me please.
蜜莉恩?
Miriam?
蜜莉恩
Miriam.
蜜莉恩?
Miriam?
救命！
Help!
为什么！究竟为什么！！
Why? Why are you doing this?
我爱你
I love you.
不论你是谁……
Whoever you are...
我求求你……
please, I'm asking you...
求你不要
Don't do this.
求你……不要伤害我的孩子
Please...don't hurt my baby.
求你了，房间里有个小孩，请不要……
Please, there's a small baby in the room, please don't...
求你别动我的孩子
Leave my baby alone please.
你对我的家人做了什么？
What have you done to my family?
把电话给他
Let me talk to him.
纳尼？
What?
让我跟我老公说
Let me talk to my husband.
是。。。是你老婆。。。。
It's... It's your wife...
S：《劈腿》
导演：胡安·马丁内斯·莫雷诺
很好
Alright.
总而言之，我们之所以选在今天对你进行试镜
Basically why we're shooting your audition today
是想让你对制片人展示自己的习惯所在
is to show the producers what you're comfortable doing,
自己的能力所长，自己的意图所指
what you're able to do,what you're willing to do...
这能反映出你对事物的态度如何
It's really like an attitude thing.
好比说，假如我让你吸我的鸡巴……
Like,if I told you to suck my dick...
……你会照做不误吗？
...would you do as you're told?
有什么问题吗？
Or would there be some sort of an issue?
那么请张开嘴
Open your mouth for me please.
很好……
Good...
你个小骚逼
You a little whore?
跟着我说
Say it.
你知道
You know...
……有很多女孩子为了得到这个机会什么都干的出来
...a lot of girls would kill for this opportunity.
所以你必须走在她们前面
So you gotta stand above the competition.
瓦屋！好恶心的眼睛！
Wow! Phew,those are some eyes!
你是瞎子？
Are you blind?
在拍戏那天，咱们要准备点，嗯
We're gonna have to get some,ah, sunglasses for her
太阳镜给她
on the day of the shoot.
我们得看看你的形体
We are gonna need to see your body.
不幸的是，制片人们都很挑剔
Unfortunately, producers are kind of picky about that kind of thing.
所以，如果你把那套逗比的裙子脱了，然后……
So if you could just take off that retarded dress that you're wearing...
快点，谢谢
Faster, please.
我们可没一整天的时间耗着，是吧？
We do not have all day, do we?
嗯……还算凑合吧
Yeah... those're okay.
C减，不能再高
I give 'em a "C-Minus"...
等下，我操，这什么鬼？
Wait! What,what the fuck is that?
- 噢，一条鸡巴……
- Oh, that's a dick...
- 我日！
- Gross!
鸡巴？得了吧，你们这帮逗货！
A dick? Come on, you guys!
你们知道来之前
How many fucking times is this gonna happen before
要经过多少次的筛选吗！？
somebody starts fucking screening the girls?!
不是鸡巴
Not a dick.
我喜欢鸡巴
I like dicks.
妈的怎么回事？
What the fuck was that?
我了个操！
Holy shit!
喔耶！喔耶！爽！爽！
Ooooh, yes...! Yes!
T：《性虐色情片》
导演：珍·索萨，西尔维娅·索萨姐妹（代表作：《非礼勿视2》，《新版血腥玛丽》
等级：6
残次品
U：《乌托邦》
导演：文森佐·纳塔利（代表作：《心慌方1》，《附身》）
嗨，亲爱的！
Hi, honey!
嗨，宝贝儿！
Hey, sweetie!
嗨
Hi!
你那边……能看到吗？
Is this... is this working?
看到了，真没想到你手机在那边还能用
Yeah, I can't believe your phone works there!
等下等下，给你看这个，看这个
Hold on, hold on,look at this, look at this.
看到了吗？
Are you seeing that?
噢，太美了
Oh wow, that is so beautiful.
极其炫丽，对吧
Tell me that's not gorgeous, right?
是啊
Yeah!
看到你的脸真的太好了
It is so good to see your face.
想死你了！
I miss you!
我更想你
I miss you more.
迪伦去哪儿了？
Where's Dylan?
我想他还在睡吧
I think he's still sleeping.
是吗？我不在他是不是很开心？
Yeah? Is he glad I'm not there?
我敢打赌他绝逼说我坏话了
I bet he's been talking shit about me.
啥？不不，根本没有……
What? No! No, not at all...
迪伦很喜欢你的，好吗
Come on...Dylan loves you, okay?
你们昨晚都干什么了？
What'd you guys do last night?
我们就走了走，溜溜弯
We literally took a walk...
……嗯，就在沙滩上，当然我们都喝了点啤酒
...uh, in the sand,and we just had a couple beers.
嗯哼，你们的基友之旅？没啥大不了的，说实话吧
Uh-huh, on your boys' trip?It's okay, you can tell me...
好吧！三瓶，真的，就这么多
Okay! Three beers.But really, that was it.
嗯，说实话……
Um, honestly, you know,
你知道我们都超级低调的
it's just... We're just keeping it super low-key.
好吧
Right.
哦，那是迪伦吗？瞧，他粗线了
Oh, is that Dylan?Look, he's right there.
哈哈是啊，他粗线了
Yeah, he's here.
等一会，哥们儿，我在打电话，等一下好吗？
Hold on, dude, I'm on the phone.Give me one second, okay?
不好意思……
I'm sorry...
嗨，迪伦
Hi, Dylan...
嗨，安波
Hi, Amber!
哥们，我跟你说了我在打电话……老兄等会，就一会……
Dude, I told you I'm on the phone,man... One second, one second...
好吧
Okay...
你们住在哪儿？给我看看你们的房间
Where are you guys staying?Show me your room!
呃，说实话，现在有点乱，你……是不会想看的……
Ah, honestly, it's a mess right now,you wouldn't... want to see it...
你想看我们的房间？
You want to see our room?
当然，给我来个全景
Yeah, give me the tour!
宝贝，我等会再打给你……
Baby, I'm going to call you back...
给她一个全景啊，伙计！
Let's give her a tour, man!
我靠，干嘛！快把电话给我！
Yo, what the fuck!Give me the phone! Dude!
把电话还我，给我……我操！
Give me my phone, give...give me... fuck!
- 宝贝儿，挂掉！
- 亲爱的，过的咋样？
- Baby, hang up...
- Hey baby, how you doin'?
迪伦，你在干嘛？
Dylan, what are you doing?
- 亲爱的！
- 嘿，嘘，别担心！
- Baby!
- Hey, shhh, don't worry!
喔喔喔，看看，这是什么？
Ohhh, look at that, what's that?
- 这是什么？
- What is that?
- What's that?
是毒品？
Are those hard drugs?
猜对了……给你介绍几个我们的小伙伴
Yeaaaah... Introduce you to some of our new friends...
……比如这位美女
...like this sweet little peach.
- 她是谁？
- Who is she?
- 顺便再看看这一位……
- Take a look at that...
- 咋样，你喜欢吗？
- Yeah, you like that?
- 她是谁？
- Who is she?
看那粉嫩的乳头
Look at those itty-bitty titties!
还记得你的奶子原来长啥样吗？我可记得哟
Remember when your titties used to look like that? I do!
操你，迪伦
Fuck you, Dylan.
我来让你看看科特的
Let me show you what Curt got.
不！不！不要看！不要看！
No, no!Look away! Look away!
你知道你男朋友喜欢熟女的老骚逼吗？
Did you know your boyfriend likes smelly old pussy?
你知道吗？
Did you know that?
瓦屋！重口味！
Wow! That's strong!
不过，有意思的是……
But, funny story...
如果你同时叫了母女二人作陪……
...you know you get a discount here
价格会便宜点噢
if you do both mother and daughter?
是啊，很变态
Yeah, it's sick!
等会……
Hold on...
让科特来接电话！你这变态！
Put Curt back on the phone!You're disgusting!
等等，那个是螺丝刀？
Wait, is that a screwdriver?
这重口味老熟女昨天用它玩了个小把戏喔……
Smelly mommy did a smelly trick with this last night...
我演示给你看看
Let me show ya.
别听他的！
Don't listen to him!
宝贝儿，别听他的！快挂电话！
Baby, don't listen to him!Hang up the phone right now!
- 别这样，老兄，淡定！
- No, man, come on!
- 给我电话！
- Give me the phone!
快挂掉！
Hang out with us!
过来，来，来
C'mere! Here, here, here.
给安波表演个，好么？
Do a show for Amber, okay?
- 快舔
- Suck him off.
- 再操一次不收费
- Fuck again is extra...
- 没问题
- No problem...
- 快停下！安波！
- Stop it! Amber!
这不是我本意，你是知道的
This is not me, and you know that, ok?
- 说真的，别说了
- Seriously, stop it.
- 我到现在为止都不清楚发生了什么！
- I don't know anything right now!
- 我已经不认识你了
- I have no idea who you are!
- 这全是迪伦干的，我发誓
- It's all Dylan, I swear, alright?
我说了停下，你这婊子！
I said stop it, you fucking whore!
安波？亲爱的？
Amber? Baby?
- 妈逼啊，哥们！
- Damn, dude!
- 亲爱的？
- Honey?
你还在吗？安波！
Are you still there? Amber!
我们玩完了！
You have lost it!
- 别别别，等下，听我说！
- No no no, wait, just listen to me!
- 你这恶心的变态！
- You are fucking psycho right now!
不，我要挂了！我受够了！我现在要挂电话了！
No, I'm hanging up! I'm done!I am hanging up right now!
不不不，听着，我是应该告诉你的！
No no no, look,I should have told you!
都是迪伦干的，我应该跟你说实话的
It was Dylan, alright?I should have told you, okay?
- 但这真的都是迪伦干的！
- But it was all Dylan, alright!
- 你这满嘴谎言的烂仔
- You are so full of shit.
跟他说这都是你干的！
Tell her it was all you!
快他妈说啊！
Fucking tell her!
伙计，跟她说都是你要找这两个女人来的！我什么都没干！
Dude, tell her you fucking brought the girls back! I didn't do anything!
别你妈逗了，这很要命的！
Stop fucking around, man,this is serious shit!
等等……
Wait a second...
老兄，快转身！老兄！操！螺丝刀，哥们！
Bro, turn around! Dude! Fuck!Screwdriver, dude!
转身！伙计！伙计！
Turn around! Dude! Dude!
噢，我操！
Oh, fuck!
哦哦……我操！
Oh! Oh my... fuck!
这门打不开！
This fucking door won't open!
停下！停下！
Stop! Stop!
不！我操！
No! Fuck!
妈逼，打不开门！
Fucking door won't open!
迪伦！
Dylan!
妈的，我要杀了你，你这婊子！
Oh, I'm going to fuck you up,bitch!
我要拿螺丝刀
I'm gonna fuckin' stab that screwdriver
捅进你的骚逼里……
right in your fucking cunt,you fucking...
告诉我他还活着……
Tell me he's okay...
你会讲英语吗？
Do you speak English?
不！！
Noooooo!
V：《假期》
导演：杰罗姆·赛博（代表作：《舞台惊魂》）
“泽伯之冠”！
Champions of Zorb.
哈尔莫尼亚正遭攻击
Harmonia is under attack.
勇猛善战的“卡西欧王子”最终会遇到他的宿敌吗？
Has the heroic Prince Casio finally met his match?
谁敢挑战“邪恶灵王泽伯”？
Who dares challenge the evil Mindlord Zorb?
别担心，“依然范特西”会来救你的
Don't worry,Fantasy Man will save you.
“依然范特西”可以帮你恐吓敌人
Terrify your opponents with the mighty Fantasy Man.
- 真心希望我们能帮助大表哥
- I wish we could help Prince Casio.
- 杜昂！
- Yeah!
现在你们可以探索泽伯之界了
Now you can explore the world of Zorb.
我们在哪儿？
Where are we?
大！表！哥！
Prince Casio!
操蛋！我们要团灭了！
We're dead! We're all fucking dead!
狗~命~啊！
Help me!
不！不要！
No! No!
谋！谋！谋啊！
No. No. No!
啥？
What?
不要害怕，殿下
Don't be scared, Princess.
是我
It's me...
依然范特西
Fantasy Man.
睡吧，粪哥，我的老盆友
Sleep, Fungor.My old friend.
快点，殿下，快到袋里来
Quickly, Princess, into the sack.
没时间了！
There's no time!
快点，快钻进袋子里！
Quickly, into the sack!
咱们要去哪儿？
Where are we going?
就快到了，殿下
Almost there, Princess...
我们就快到了
We're almost there.
不，不，不！
No, no, no!
W：《愿望》
导演：斯蒂文·克斯坦斯基（代表作：《父亲节》，《生化人》）
X：《木琴》
导演：朱利安·莫利和亚历山大·布斯蒂罗（代表作：《身在其中》，《死色》）
爸爸
不
武田先生
还记得我的太郎吗？
我最爱的狗狗
如果当初你好好地照看他
他现在一定还活得好好的
一星期的照看而已
这都不能好好照顾他
太郎在你来之前就已经是我们家庭的一员了
工作工作，你可是在家不用出门的工作啊
可当我回家时
太郎的脚上已经爬满了蛆虫
所有我养的花儿也都枯死了
从此我再也不可能指望你了
也开始憎恶起你的一切
你的气味
所有的一切
都是那么地恶心
你甚至连牙都不刷
留着它们还有什么用
没有吉他的才能
所以你选择放弃吉他手的身份
而成为一个老师，多可悲！
你不是说要出门的么？
哈鸭库，顺便帮我买些卸妆水
妈妈？
还记得学校所担心的
在家的饭食吗？
从来没有蔬菜，因为你不喜欢吃
你从来不烹饪你买来的料理
任由他们坏掉
你女儿的午饭全是垃圾食品
油腻腻的
屋子从来不打扫
欲求不满
武田先生的性冷淡令你永远那么饥渴
走开！
一直把欲求不满带来的焦躁发泄在我头上
适可而止吧！
我最为耿耿于怀的是：
你对我的皮疹漠不关心
难耐瘙痒的我用力挠着
以至于那些疤痕伴随我至今
你甚至记不得我对鸡蛋过敏
没能力抚养一个孩子
那你就别生出来啊！
你永远都不会了解我的感受
被夹在中间
美雪
帮我买些烟回来好吗？
到底走不走啊你？
杵在那干嘛？
态度好一点
拜托她帮你带东西的
那你去帮我买啊
哎哟哟，就跟你的吉他亲热呢
不
我再也，不去了！
Y：《青春》
导演：梅泽素一（日）
别离开我
Don't leave me...
泰，求你了别离开我
Don't leave me, Ti, please.
助产士说嚼些这个可以延缓婴儿出生
The midwife said chewing on Portlock root
就这样等我回来吧
will slow down the baby until I can get her from town.
一点一点吃
Just take small bites.
不，泰，求你了，我不想一个人呆在这，求你了
Oh Ti, please don't leave.I don't want to be alone, please.
你不会有事的
You'll be fine,
那罐子里装的药够你吃几年的
there's years enough root in that jar,
一半都不用吃完
and she's not even half a day out.
泰！回来，我不想再孤身一人了，求你了，泰
Come back Ti, I don't wanna be alone again. Please, Ti!
泰
Ti!
13年后
泰！
Ti!
泰！？
Ti?
是他么，妈妈？
Is it him, Mama?
不，不是他，宝贝
No, it's not sweetie.
你抓到什么了？妈妈？
What did we catch, Mama?
一只老兔子
A mean old bunny rabbit.
妈妈，为什么你等着兔子撞到陷阱里来
Mom, why don't you go out and catch the rabbit
而不是出去抓兔子呢？
instead of waiting for it to get trapped?
我不可能挺着个大肚子到处去抓兔子呀
I can't be running around looking for rabbit with you inside of me.
那你就让我出来嘛
You should let me come out then.
为什么要出来？不想再和妈妈呆着吗？
Why do you want to come out?Don't you like spending time with your mom?
不... 不是的
No, it's not that...
我听你的意思好像是想离开这地方丢下妈妈一人
Well, it sounds to me like you wanna leave your mom in this place all by herself.
我不是这个意思
That's not what I meant.
如果连你也走了我真的不知道该怎么活下去
Don't know what I'd do if you left me here all alone.
对不起妈妈，我只是不想总是天天吃一样的东西
I'm sorry Mama,I'm just sick of eating the same
things all the time is all.
等你爸爸回来你就能出来了
Well, you can come out when your dad gets back.
如果你是男孩，他还可以带你去打猎
And if you're a boy, he can take you out when he goes hunting.
真希望我是个男孩
I hope I'm a boy.
你爸一回来我们就知道了
Well, he'll be back any day now.We'll find out then.
但现在，你只是个小宝宝
But for now you're just a little baby.
妈妈你还好吗？
You alright, Mama?
哪去了
Where is it?
还有一块的，我记得还有一块的！
There was a piece left,I know there was some left.
什么还有一块？
Where's what?
妈妈的药
Mama's medicine.
冷静，妈妈，你让我出来吧
Calm down Mama,you gotta let me come out now.
你答应过不会离开我的！
You promised,you said you won't leave.
但我太大了，而且那药让我难受
But I'm too big,and it's hurting me.
你出来！我保证不打死你！
Don't you leave me!
我不会离开你的，妈妈
I won't leave you, Mama.
没事的妈妈，我在这儿，冷静
It's OK, Mama, I'm here,just calm down.
别离开我...
You can't leave.
不会的，妈妈，我不会离开的
Don't worry Mama,I'm not leaving.
我不想再孤身一人
I don't wanna be alone again.
我不会离开你的，妈妈，我只是需要一些空间，好吗？
I won't leave you, Mama.I just need the room, OK?
别担心，我能处理好的，妈妈，冷静下来
Don't worry, I can fix this Mama,just stay calm.
看，妈妈，现在我俩都有容身之处了
See, Mama?Now there's room for both of us.
泰，是你吗？
Ti, is that you?
我看起来真的和以前那么不一样吗？
Do I really look that different?
你上哪儿去了？
Where have you been?
无可奉告
Don't start.
我尽可能等，但是没办法，胎位不正
I waited as long as I could,but it didn't sit right.
我只能自己剖腹产了
I had to cut it out myself.
那我们只能再试一次了
Then we'll just have to try again.
我不知道我还行不行
I don't know if I can.
你当然行了
Of course you can.
Z：《受精卵》
导演：克里斯·纳什（加）
26种死法2
下课
《26种新死法》全片完  谢谢观赏
=====百度悬疑片吧字幕组=====
汉大将军袁绍   vittiger双鱼
亡灵的守护骑士 水浒三国金刚
（后面还有个小彩蛋）
《人体蜈蚣2》男主劳伦斯·R·哈维客串
让我们一同期待《人体蜈蚣3》和《26种死法3》
我真醉了。。看这种烂片我居然也能撸？
I mean, how the fuck am I meant to wank to that?